谨以此片追忆逝去的童年，如果你也有这样的童年的话欢迎加入我们的贴吧"神剑传奇"。本作品之片源来自互联网，版权归原公司所有。任何组织和个人不得公开传播或用于任何商业盈利用途，一切后果由该组织或个人承担！制作者不承担任何法律及连带责任！请自觉于下载后24小时内删除。如果喜欢本片，请购买正版！
F
2.∈
传司
F
2.∈ (ipse An
传
France 2. Etipse Animation, Toonean Productions Xll Inc
FrAnce2.∈upr
翻译：英语辅导频道
输入/时间轴/压制：harry159821/黑月
SCRIDC
D
ominiquc Lac
校对：
BCRip oy
Dominigue lacid
LNE
By the magic
that flows in my veins
在魔法的作用下跟着我的意向走
有w
What once was, shall be again
曾经出现过的东西会再重现
Powers lost
shall be regained
失去的法力会复得
Walka
沃卡
Here he
他来了
第？集
线
Take me to your mistress
带我去见你们的女主人
e
Welcome to- my lair, Bragan
欢迎大驾光临布拉刚
A
I took this from her chamber
这是我从她寝宫里拿来的
It could only belong to Djana
只可能是裘娜的私人物品
It's perfect, Bragan. Perfect!
太好了布拉刚真不错
军ed- sRe! WEB<R auia!Av
The spell works quickly
魔咒很快生效了
Soon Djana will
become disoriented
快裘娜会失去判断力
and I can take her
under my complete control
然后她就完全任我摆布了
hope you know
what you're doing, Walka
希望你很清楚自己在干什么沃卡
If Kwodahn finds out
that we're acting alone
旦科沃达发现我们擅自行动
he'll be furious
他会勃然大怒的
He won't be angry very long
when we bring him Xcalibur!
我们呈上神剑他就不会生气太久的
Yes, Xcalibur
没错神剑
And, using Djana this way has
nothing to do with your desire
何况这样利用裘娜
to regain your Sylph powers
跟你想恢复精灵的法力无关
Of course not
当然无关
That is merely an added benefit
to an otherwise excellent plan
那不过是这个完美计划的附加收益罢了
It smells done to me. Herik
闻起来好象可以了哈里克
You shouldn't
overcook Fangor, you know
要知道你可不能烤过头了
it dries,out
否则就焦了
What is it. Diana?
裘娜
语
Did you hear that?
听到了吗
Come and get it
过来吃点吧
It must have been an anima
肯定是动物发出的声音
What smel?… he roast?
什么味道你是烤吗
Smells good to me!
真香
As good as it tastes!
味道也不错
Someones watching us
有人在看着我们
I feel it
我感觉到了
Don't be afraid
别害怕我没有恶意
ike me, you are
a child of Nature
和我一样你也是大自然的孩子
You you can speak?
你会说话啊
haven t heard or
felt anything unusu
我没听到也没有感觉到任何不正常
Have you
你呢
Were all tired, Herik
我们都累了哈里克
Our senses aren
as sharp as usua
我们的感官没有平时敏锐
Maybe
也许
b
Maybe
也许
just hope Djana's
not starting to hallucinate
我只希望裘娜不是开始幻觉
or getting paranoid
或者得妄想症了
Hallucinate? Paranoid?
觉妄想
How could you even
oke/ about Djana that way?
怎么可仪这样拿裘娜开玩笑
If she says she heard
something, I believe her
地说她听到了什么我就相信她
All right
Keep your scales on, Wip
行当心一点威普
e only hunt to feed ourselves
我们狩猎只是为了填饱肚子
Yes, I agree
it is cruel and unfair
没错是很残忍很不公平
Of course,
I could be hallucinating
当然我可能会产生幻觉
Maybe the roast wasn't
all that good after all
也许烤肉井没有那么美味吧
Yeah, I'm definitely hearing things
没错我确实听到什么
It was a Fangor
是头梵高
Everything all right: Djana?
没事吧裘娜
Sure
当然
Good night
晚安
Don't you want any of my roast?
你不吃点烤肉吗
Wip can have my share.
把我那份给威普吧
Nell, to tell you the truth
老实说
I'm not really hungry
我不怎么饿
First Djana, now Wip
先是裘娜现在是威普
Dont stand so close. Bragan
别站那么近布拉刚
Your plan makes
me uncomfortable Walka
你的计划让我感觉不舒服沃卡
Reviving Djana's Sylph
powers can backfire on us
唤醒裘娜的精灵法力可能会引火上身
Isn't Xcalibur worth
a little risk to you?
难道神剑不值得你冒险一试吗
Well, never fear, my brave prince
我的亲王你不是从来不怕的吗
Her powers will
be under my control!
她的那点法力会在我的掌控之中
Djana: . Djana
裘娜裘娜
Who's there? Who are you?
谁在那你是谁啊
m
Djana. Djana
裘娜裘娜
Tara? Herik?
塔拉哈里克
Wip?
威普
Diana
裘娜
A
Mother!
母后
it reall
真的是你吗
have returned to
emind you of your heritage
我是想趁你完全忘记我之前
before you forget me completely.
回来提醒你有关遗传的事
Mother, you and Father
are always in my thoughts
母后我时刻想着你和父王
As the daughter
of a Sylph, Djana
裘娜你是精灵的女
you have a special calling
a duty to serve nature
因此你有一种特殊的使命
和责任为大自然服务
as you have turned away from me
那就如同背弃了我
BAEH RS7 Sh
as you have turned away from me
那就如同背弃了我
If you do not change
your ways, she will disown you
如果你不作出改变她就会不认你
I don't understand. Mother
我不明白母后
what should i do?
我该怎么做
号
What? What is it?
Another talking Fangor?
什么什么东西又一个会说话的梵高吗
忘
Did you have
a bad dream>Djana?
做噩梦了吗娜
She... There was
我她那里
Yes a dream
是的
dream!
Where are we going
我们要去哪
k
You don't have to come with me
你们不用跟着我
k
he heck we don't
干吗不要我们一起啊
y
All right, Herik
I admit Djana isnt well
哈里克我也觉得裘娜有点不对劲
But if it's not
just fatigue, what is it?
可如果不是疲劳所致又会是什么呢
Stop saying that
不要再那么说了
There's nothing wrong
with Princess Djan
裘娜公主没什么不对劲
拳
A
All right, I'll try
好我试试
Now she's talking to a tree
现在她居然跟一棵树说话了
That' s a new one
真是新奇
Actually… last night
she talked to a Fangor
其实昨晚她是跟一头梵高在说话
乡
Smoldering
g
sulfur
now did she do that?
不可能吧她怎么做到的
Only a sylph has that
kind of power over nature
只有精灵才有那种超自然的法力
hink I know what's happening.
我想我知么回事了
Djana's.mother was a Sylph
娜的母亲是精灵
and she's having, a little
trouble getting used to them
然后她还不太习惯那些法力的存在
But why would they
appear so suddenly, right now?
什么那些法力现在才突然出现呢
Yes, it has been a
long time since it rained
是好久没下雨了
But don't worry, I'll help you
不过别担心我会帮你的
It wants to flower
她想开花
That's enough
够了
Where are you taking us Djana
裘娜你要带我们去哪
And what do you
do there?
那做什么
Im going to fulfil my destiny
我正在履行我的使命
You can't stop me, nothing can
你们不能阻止我没什么可以阻止我
M
Diana! What are you doing?
裘娜你在干什么啊
Djana! Come back!
裘娜回来
You don't understand!
你们不懂的
个
We want -to help you. Djana
我们想帮你裘
Everything.
gding according to plan
都在照计划进行
Here comes Djana, all alone.
裘娜来
大来的
aEpe
Here comes Djana, all alone
裴娜来了一个大来的
What a good little soldier
多棒的小战士啊
she even fought it
out with her friends
居然跟自己的朋友打起来了
Wait! I'll have to take-Xcalibur
等等我得去把神剑拿到手
since you. can't touch-it yoursel
因为你不能碰它
No! She mustn't see you
不在我完全控制她之前
before I've gained
full control over her
不能让她见到你
I'm not in the habit
of obeying orders, Walka
我可不习惯服从人家的命令沃
I give them
向来是我下命令给别人
Not this time
这次不行
If you're restless, Bragan
布拉刚如果你坐立不安的话
you acan keep yourself busy
就让自己忙起来
by staking the Book of
ife from Djana,s companions
去裘娜的同伴那拿来生命之书
They may still
be a problem for us
他们也许还是个麻烦
My Golgotha will help you
我的魔兽会一旁协助你
You'l join me later.
你晚点跟我会
Yes. I'll take care
f the little monk
行我去招呼那个小术士
and his Barbarian friend
和他的蛮族人朋友
And once get Xcalibur,
旦我得到神剑
your attitude will change, witch
你的态度就会转变巫婆
Go on, ugly brutes
Find me that Shog
走吧恶心的函我找到那个小术土
I can t reach my sword!
我够不着我的剑
can't move either
我也动不了
How could she do this to us?
她怎么能够这样对待我们
Ho
Hey! That works
What do you know?
嘿成功了你们呢
Wip! That's it
Keep burning the vines
威普就是那样持续烧这些树藤
b
Great job!
Great job
干得不错
e got to find
where Djana went. Quick!
我们得知道裘娜去哪了快
Diana is headed
ght for Walka's lair
表娜朝沃的巢穴去
Walka! Why am l not surprised?
是沃卡怎么我一点都不吃惊
处
Walka was\ a sylph once. too
沃曾经也是精灵
Funny that Diana's going to her
真有
卡的精灵法力再现
just, when her own
Sylph powers reappeared
娜就跑去找她
doub
a coincidence
我觉得这不是巧合
But, Princess Djana would never do
anything bad with her Sylph powers
可裘娜公主不会用精灵法力去做坏事啊
The Sylphs magic is good magic
精灵法力是善良的法力
That all depends on
who is in control, Wi
那就要看谁在操控威普
and right now
I don' t / think it's Diana.
而现在我不认为那个人是裘娜
I know a shortcut along the coast
我知道沿着海边有条捷径
We can get
there before she does
走那条路我们可以比裘娜先到
nF
票
A
princess
公殿下
well see if you are really
a good, obedient daughter.
现在让我们看看你是不是
个真正乖巧的女
Were almost there.
我们快到了
小
We'llleave the
horses here out of si
ight
我们让马儿呆在这里避大眼目
We're-close enough to the pond
我们离池塘太近了
Just in time. too
正好及时赶到
Djana will-be here any second
裘娜马上就会到了
Oh no! Not those
stinking golgoth
哦不那些腐臭的兽
Your-reflexes
aren't very sharp
作为年轻人
for such/a young man
你的反应真不敏捷
Let's. see how good
yours are old tyrant!
让我们看看你的反应有多好老暴君
Against you
Barbarian, I wouldn't worry
蛮族人对付你我不用担心
Wip! Find Djana
and keep an eye on her.
威普去找裘娜帮她照看一下
Ok. But Dwon' t be
able to do much for her.
好可我帮不了她太多
rWe'll catch up
with-you when we can
可以的话我们会尽快赶过去
hat is, if we can
就那样如果可以的话
Oh! Why do I always
get the hard jobs?
噢为什么每次把艰巨的任务交给我啊
Diana? Where are you?
裘娜你
Huh? Princess Saphire
That's impossible!
啊索非亚公主不可能
Dirty little insect!!
恶心的小昆虫
You are not
going to spoil my: plan!
你不是来坏我好事的吧
Ahl-Help
Good riddance
总算解决了
了
Getting tired, Barbarian?
累了吧蛮族人
Not ye
还没呢
N
Ugly and not very smart
又丑又笨
The poor things
可怜的东西
If youll excuse.me
失陪了
have a sword to
retrieve and a kingdom to rule
我得拿到神剑然后统治这个王国
Coward
胆小鬼
I won't let you get
away with the Book of Life!
我不会让你拿走生命之书的
There are too many of them
他们数量众多啊
秒
w
e
后
Mother
母后
Motheroel've come for your help
后一我是来向你求助的
don' t know
what you expect of me
我不知道你对我有什么期待
I wasn t there to guide
you, my little princess
是我没能好好引导你我的小公
e It isn't your fault
这不是你的错
t
s这
n
you厂faut
这不是你的错
It isn't
It was the humans
who led you astra
是人类让你走上了迷途
They have corrupted
with Xcalibur, a weapon of stee
他们用那把破铁所谓的神剑误导了你
斗工昔耍申闻雒雅留[
uodeaM B 'Inq!e。×uM
noA panda.Io=e∧euo
They have corrupted you
with Xcalibur,a weapon of steel
他们用那把破铁所谓的神剑误导你
You are a Sylph, Djana
精灵裘娜
a protector of
nature. not a vandal
是大自然的保护人而不是破坏者
You must rid yourself of
this vulgar weapon, my daughter.
你得自己摆脱这把破剑我的女儿
要
v
Hurry up. Herik
They 're wearing me) down
快点哈里克我挡不他们了
N
Balls of fir
趁现在火球去
N
Nice shot, Herik!
正中目标哈里克
Are you alright?
你还好吧
It took a lot out
but I'm oka
刚才那已我耗损太多不过还媒
Let's find Djana!
我们去找裘娜吧
And then get the Book
of Life back from/ Bragan!
然后从布拉刚那把生命之书拿回来
You must rid yourself of
this vulgar weapon my- daughter
你得自己摆脱这把破剑我的女儿
Humans
:求它属
It belongs to Humans
它属于人类
whose sordid
affairs are beneath you
他们的这些贪婪事有失你的身份
三
了
Yes, mother. You're right
是的母后你说得对
Unburden yourse
Diana
卸下这个重吧妍
Give up the sword
弃这把剑
Let the humans
deal their own justice
让人类他们自己分配公平
that is no concern of yours
那都不是你要担心的事
Trust me and
hand over the sword
信我把神剑交出来
Oh, my head
哦我的头
What a dumb
place to put a tree,
这该死的地方怎么会有棵树
Djana! No! Donit do-it
裘娜不要不要那么做
That's not your mother
jana, it's Alkal
那不是你母亲裘娜是沃卡
jana. it's walk
那不是你费绑是沃
That's not your mother
Diana, it's Walke
那不是你母绑是沃美
See how- freely
they lie to you, Djana
悲那看他们对你撇谎如此自然啊
Don't be fooled!
别被他愚弄了
M
回aNo
楼加不要
Diana! No!
裘娜不要
让
零
You burned me
你烧到我了
Praimcessoosal'm so sorry
公主殿下抱歉
..I was frightened a
我刚才被吓到了
Well done, my daughter
得好我的女儿
Now complete your
deed and fetch the sword
现在完成你自己的事把剑拾起来
Saphire?
是索非亚吗
That,'s impossible
那不可能
It must be an
illusion created by Walka
肯定是沃卡弄出来的幻象
Shes using it
to manipulate diana
她利用这个方法来摆布裘娜
cThat explains Djana's
break with reality
就解释裘娜反常的原因了
She'd believe anything
只要是她认为是她母亲说的
if she thought it
o came from her mother.
她都会相信
∠E
You are a sylph, Djana
If you serve Nature
你是个精灵裘娜要是你为大自然服务
Djana! ['m choking
裘娜我要窒息了
h
Let me go!
放开我
Can you break Walka's spell?
你能破除沃卡的魔咒吗
d育
The book says l need alink
that is closely-related to Walka
生命之书说我需要一件跟沃卡
密切相关的东西才能破解
like a fingernail, or a hair
比如说一颗指甲一根头发什么的
There!
That's one of her feathers
那里
根她的羽毛
That should work
那个应该就可以
Power of wind fly
风球去
会
Xcalibur Atlast!
神剑终到
Ye
没错
Let the truth be revealed!
让真相大白吧
=
Diana
娜
裘娜
What… what a
doing here
我在这做什么
Walka tricked you, Djana
沃
卡骗了你裘娜
But you have
your Sylph powers now.
可你现在有精灵的法力了
Don' t be afraid to use them!
不要怕勇敢使用吧
ip go
放开威普
A
Thank goodness
I was beginning to cramp up
谢天谢地我刚差点抽筋了
What are you waiting for?
你在等什
Destroy them
们
May watersome murder drown you
让水淹没你们吧
Can you spare a minute?
你可以给我一分钟吗
You only have your
powers because of me!
我给了你精灵法力
And I can take them away
我也可以把他们都消除
Little fool! We will
meet again, princess
小笨蛋我们会再见面的公主殿
THats right, Bagan!=
那就对了人布拉
Run back to your beloved witch!
逃回你亲爱的女身边吧
Dianasare you all right?
裘娜你没事吧
I'm okay, Tara, thanks.
我很好塔拉谢谢
Of course she's okay
她当然没事啦
Nothing like a quick di
to make you feel refreshed
没有比在水里泡过一次更让人精神振奋了
e
Aev
Okay, so we have a deal, then?
那我们做个约定吧如何
It's not that
Idon't like flowers
并不是我不喜欢花
but it is a little disturbing
不过确实是有点
Wip! stop it!
威普打住
That's Djana's heritage
you're talking about
你说的是裘娜遗传的东西
Herik
没关系哈里克
i It's okay, Herik
After -what happened to him
历了那些之后
Wip has a good reason
to mistrust Sylph magic
威普有理由怀疑精灵的法力
Besides, that's not really
what my mother left me anyway.
况且那并不真是我母后遗传给我的
My mother gave up
her life as a Sylph
为了对我父王的爱
for the love of my father
我母后献出了她的精灵生命
or the I县
裴后献了她的精生命
for the love of my father.
我母后献出了她的精灵生命
Thats her true legacy.
d my true heritage
就是她真正遗传给我的
to follow your heart
and put love above all else
就是跟随自己的心让爱高于一切
You are right, princess
你说得对公主殿下
Love is much more
precious than magic
爱可比法力珍贵多了
SCRIPT SUPERYISOR
SCRIPT CONSULTANT
SCRIPT SUPERYISORD
IEcuTIYE STORy EDITOR
RIPT CONSULTANT
SToR
可°Me3815
STUDIO MANIE
TulO
STUDIO MANKGEK. ELLIPSE
PRODUCTION KDMIMISTKAT
NCAH PRODUCTIONS II nIC.
PRODUCTION AOMIMISTRK
是 NOON PRODUCTIONS I INC.
3D-MODELING
3D MODELING
GRIBOUILLE
RIBOUILLE
STeg rtos
PROoUC
CTION: TSSISTTIT
AIRUPETRON
段H
wan segre
E
PROOUCTION
PRODUCTIO
PRoDuC
DITD HRMNTT吧
OGRAPH
SUPERTISORS
器
SOFTwIRe DeveLoPER
Errror
m
1o
C6 RTISTS
否AMre
DNLL
43 ayW
H
贴eh
MOTION CAPTURE
SILICON STUDIO
MOTION CKPTURE
C6C6 INC
H
c∈C6Nc
erecummiN Skim uceR
RODUCTION"器
PeRYISOR
CGCG IN
PRODUGD SsRO riso
翻译：英语辅导频道
输入/时间轴/压制：harry159821/黑月
校对：